Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series V. Gigs
  - Wellesley College [reading] 1991 Nov. 3 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Whatcom Museum, Bellingham, Washington [reading / performance] 1991 Oct. 12 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Wildcat Words [reading] 1992 Oct. 11 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Williams College [reading] 1994 Apr. 25 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Women and Children too / a Woman's place bookstore [reading or speaking request] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - The Women's Building, San Francisco [Wolverton, Terry] [reading with Ana Castillo] 1986 Aug. 15 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - The Women's Building, San Francisco "A celebration of Women's gifts" [speaking] 1994 Sept. 24 -25 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Women's Mural Building Project "Poetry and Paint" [reading] 1994 June (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Yale University Race, Ethnicity, and Body Image [panel discussion] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - YWCA DramaDIVAS performance [reading / speaking] 1993 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Series VI. Manuscripts by others
  - Acosta, Belinda. "El museo de Lucia Herminia: a new play" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    TMs, 35 pp.
  - Alarcón, Norma. "La Malinche: from Tenochtitlán to Aztlán" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    TMs, 17 pp.
  - Allison, Dorothy. "A bastard out of Carolina" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allison, Dorothy. "Myth and Image" 1985 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allison, Dorothy. Notes on manuscripts n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allison, Dorothy. "A personal history of Lesbian porn," New York Native (1982 May 24 - June 6): 22 - 23 1982 May 24 -June 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allison, Dorothy. "Public silence, private terror" 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    TMs, 20 pp.
  - Allison, Dorothy. "The women that hate me" series 1982 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    6 TMs, 16 pp.
  - "The Americas: introduction" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    TMs, 33 pp.
  - Anzaldúa, Gloria. "El paisano is a bird of good omen: from a novel in progress" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    TMs, 26 pp.
  - Arellano, Cathy. "My Diez y sies de Septiembre 1987: Cherríe Moraga from pages to person" 1989 May 25 -1995 Mar. 31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    TMs, 1 p.; TLS; ANS
  - Arroyo, María Isabel Baez & Ana Irma Rivera Lassen. ...Y algo mas. Rio Piedros, Puerto Rico: Caller Feminista n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    TMs, unpaginated
  - Barrera, Mario. "My life among the Gopis" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    TMs, 34 pp.; ALS
  - Bridgeforth, Sharon. "Lovve / rituals & rage" and "Tribute" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bright Fires anthology. "April's long hot summer" 1987 Apr. 24 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brodine, Karen. supplement to Freedom Socialist (1988 Feb. - Apr.): 3 - 14 1988 Feb. -Apr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Castillo, Ana. "Daddy with Chesterfields in a rolled up sleeve" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Castillo, Ana. "Dirty Mexican" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Castillo, Ana. "¿Donde empezar?" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Castillo, Ana. drawings n.d. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Castillo, Ana. "For Jean Ryes (1890 - 1979)" 1986 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Castillo, Ana. "For the woman who doesn't (love men: you must always maintain a sense of humor)" 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Castillo, Ana. "How we laughed" and "Cacophony," Poetry SF.-- No. 4 (1986 Spring) 1986 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Castillo, Ana. "I am the daughter / Mother who has learned" 1986 Aug. 24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Castillo, Ana. "Ixtacihuatl Died in Vain" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Castillo, Ana. "A Monchi poem" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Castillo, Ana. "No Solo el ser Chilena" 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Castillo, Ana. "Swimming from the wreck" and notes n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Castillo, Ana. "Tejido de pelo y dientes" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chandy, Sunu P. "Audacious sisters of color writing group," Earlham College Senior Project 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - de Lauretis, Teresa. The Practice of Love, chapter 5 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    reprint, 50 pp.; ANS
  - de Monteflores, Carmen. "Blood lines" 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    TMs, 116 pp.
  - Earth Summit 1992 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Enriquez, Sam. "Indians walk 3,500 miles with message of unity," Los Angeles Times (1996 Feb.) 1996 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Escamill, Edna. "The great desert is full" and "Promises broken, promises kept," Matrix.--Vol. 8, no. 7 (1983 Nov.) 1983 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Espinosa, Fabian. Aji Aji. 1987 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    TMs, 38 pp.; ALS
  - Galindo, Martivón. "Desde el 'American dream': poesia" 1989 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    TMs, 64 pp.
  - Galindo, Mary Sue. "Te habla tu Papá" c. 1985 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Galleano, Eduardo. "¿Qué camino para la izquierda?" and "Some things death can't kill" 1988 -1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. 3 poems ["The movement in a human heart obeys such rules," "The words 'begin again'," and "Entries: L.A. Log"] 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    3 TMs, 3 pp.
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. Building some changes. Venice, CA: Beyond Baroque New Book 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    TMs, 22 pp.
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "The death I want" 1978 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Dreaming of Athena" 1981 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Finally" 1977 Nov. 26 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Going away" 1978 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "I name your love for me" 1978 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "I spent the day with you" 1978 Mar. 10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Identifying the feeling" 1978 Feb. 4 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "It could have all happened and part of it did" 1978 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. poems written on archaic forms and notes n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "A preface" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Sebastopol Saturday Afternoon" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "Things happening on the roads going fast" 1977 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "This is not making love" 1978 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "You must change your life" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Healy, Eloise Klein. "You won't love me and I learn death" 1978 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Herrera, Gloria & Jeanette Lizcano. "La mujer Chicana" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    TMs, 38 pp.
  - Herrera-Eichler, Yvonne. Hijas del sol (Daughters of the sun): a Play. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    TMs, 33 pp.; ANS
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "Amber & Jeff's notes to SR [Socialist Review] Collective" 1980 Oct. 31 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    AMs (reprint), 4 pp.
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "The barren expanse of lonliness," New York Native (1983 Nov. 21 - Dec. 3) 1983 Nov. 21 -Dec. 3 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "The erotophobic voice of women: building a movement for the 19th century," New York Native (1983) 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "Feminist Anger, Sexual desire, erotophobia in the anti-porn women's movement" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    TMs (reprint), 12 pp.
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "The gap she fostered," New York Native (1984 Jan. 2 - 15) 1984 Jan. 2 -15 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber, an interview with [by Sarah Schulman], Womanews n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. Interview, Gay Left n.d. [c. 1979] (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "The intimate signs of wear," New York Native (1984 Feb. 27 - Mar. 11) 1984 Feb. 27 -Mar. 11 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "Remembering" 1982 Sept. 30 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    TMsS, 4 pp.
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "Surf Nazis," New York Native (1983 May 23 - June 5) 1983 May 23 -June 5 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Hollibaugh, Amber. "A Touch of class," New York Native (1983 June 20 - July 3) 1983 June 20 -July 3 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - International Women's Day '84 Coalition Statement of Unity. "Woemn unite: for human needs, not war!" 1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Ladha, Yasmin. "Bridal hands on the maple" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Latin American Theatre Artists Mission Statement / organizational handbook 1991 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ledesma, Alberto. "Las voces obscuras de un sotano invisible" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    TMs, 23 pp.
  - Ledesma, Alberto. "Poetry for homeboys on the foul line" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Ledesma, Alberto. Untitled manuscript and research materials on Richard Rodriguez [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    TMs, 14 pp.
  - Ledesma, Alberto. Untitled manuscript and research materials on Richard Rodriguez [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Lorde, Audre. Notes from Audre Lorde discussion at Cazenovia Women Writers Conference n.d. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Lucero, Judy (Convict #21918). 6 poems. n.d. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Lujan, Jaime. "Heroes and Saints: Cerezita Valle -- A Masters Thesis" 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    TMs, unpaginated; ANS
  - Martinez, Elizabeth. "'Chignon Politics' Die Hard: reflections on the first Chicano Activists reunion," Z Magazine (1990 Apr.): 46 - 50 1990 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Matos-Cintrón, Nemir. Las mujeres no hablan así c. 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    TMs (reprint)
  - Montoya, Gina. "Bueno Bye! Cherri [sic] Moraga" 1986 Mar. 27 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    2 TMs, 2 pp.; ANS
  - Moyano, Anacleto Rodriguez. "La piquer Viva: 26 canciones de Leyenda" n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pérez, Emma M. "Los Perros Horribles" 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Pérez, Emma M. "Mujer Cariñosa" 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Pérez, Emma M. "To the schism in our sisterhood" 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pérez, Julia. Untitled 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    TMs, 66 pp.; ANS
  - Philips, Frances. Poems 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    TMs, 10 pp.; TLS
  - Public School 3B. A hand coming out of my mouth" n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Quintanales, Mirtha N. "Home again, home: excerpt from a diary" 1984 June (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Quintanales, Mirtha N. "Massachusetts Valley" 1982 May (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Quintanales, Mirtha N. "El penultimo viaje" c. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Quintanales, Mirtha N. Untitled n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    TMs, 12 pp.
  - Rangel, Yolanda. Untitled ("I had 2 abortions...) 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    TMs, 1 p.; ALS
  - Rivera-Valdés, Sonia. "Ana le pide una varita mágica a los Reyes Magos" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rivera-Valdés, Sonia. "En Thanksgiving te regalaban un paro. O Los Ojos lindos de Adela" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    TMs, 11 pp.
  - Saenz, Diana E. "Celebracion of the dead" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    TMs, 54 pp.; 2 photographs: col.; 10 x 14 cm.
  - Saenz, Diana E. "Lorca at Vizner" 1991 Jan. 24 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    TMs, 27 pp.
  - Salazar Parreñas, Celine. "Mahal means love & expensive (some poems)" 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Salazar Parreñas, Celine. Poems 1992 May 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sanchez-Padilla, Beverly. "The memmi, Fanon, Fanomena" 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    TMs (transparency), 1 p.
  - Savigliano, Marta E. "Political Economy of Passion: Tango, Exoticism, and Decolonization" 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    TMs, 229 pp.
  - Shebar-Windstone. "Muriel Rukeyser: a life in poetry," New Women's Times Feminist Review (1979 May 11 - 24): 10 - 13 1979 May 11 -24 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Silvas, Helen. "The frijoles are burning" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    TMs, 32 pp.
  - Sisqueiros, Symona. 7 poems n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Som, Indigo Chih-Lien. "Under the moons of my fingernails" c. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    TMs, 65 pp.
  - Vaeth, Kimberly Joynes. Unpacking from the trip: poems 1980 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    TMs, 47 pp.
  - Villanueve, Alma. "Her choice" c. 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Walker, Alice. "What can the White man... say to the Black Woman?" The Nation (1989 May 22): 691 - 692 1989 May 22 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Woo, Merle. "Yellow woman speaks: selected poems" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Yarbro-Bejarano, Yvonne. "Chicano Literature from a Chicana Feminist Perspective" 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    TMs, 25 pp.
  - Young, Leslie. "Prelude" 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - [Unidentified author]. "Chicken lady," Off our backs (1979 July): 24 1979 July (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "A bastard out of Carolina: a novel" n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    TMs, 458 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "Demon" 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "Don't tell me you don't know" 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "Don't tell me you don't know" n.d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "Doreen" 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy. "Predators" n.d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    TMs, 31 pp.
  - [RESTRICTED] Allison, Dorothy.Untitled story 1985 Feb. 4 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - [RESTRICTED] Cervantes, Lorna Dee. "Letters to David: an Elegiac Mass in the Form of a Train" 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Series VII. Cultural Work
  - Artistas Indígenas n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gulf War [includes CM's original arrest report for Gulf War Protest] 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian Gay, Mexican-Latin American organizations [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lesbian Gay, Mexican-Latin American organizations [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lesbian and Gay activism n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights in Nicaragua [Malespín, Guadalupe Sequeria] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Latino Communications Center n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Necessary Bread Disarmament Statement; Anti-War activism materials n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Plaza de la Raza n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Quincentenario [NACLA Report on the Americas.--Vol. 24, nos. 5 - 6; vol. 25, nos. 2 - 3] [1 of 2] 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Quincentenario [2 of 2] 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Race, religion, ethnicity n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [1 of 6] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [2 of 6] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [3 of 6] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [4 of 6] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [5 of 6] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Rape, sexual assault, domestic violence [includes: resources for Women of Color Conference] [6 of 6] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Women of Color, domestic violence [miscellaneous conference materials] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Theater Correspondence, 1990s
  - American Conservatory Theatre 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Place Theatre 1991 June 12 -Dec. 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - At the foot of the mountain [Reneé, Dawn] [1 of 2] 1984 -1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - At the foot of the mountain [2 of 2] 1984 -1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Borderlands Theater 1992 Dec. 23 -1993 Sept. 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brava! for women in the arts [Rosenberg, Shoshana] 1994 Sept. 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carillo, Juliette 1992 Apr. 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Celebration Theatre 1987 Oct. 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - City Lights Theatre Company 1992 Sept. 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dramatic Publishing Company n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Frockt, Deborah [Actors Theatre of Louisville] 1991 Oct. 24 -1992 Mar. 24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Frontera Productions, Austin, Texas 1994 June (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glickman, Will Theatre Fund / Will Glickman Playwright Award [Rosenblum, Bobo] 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Heroes & Saints, miscellaneous correspondence & Heroes & Saints contact sheet 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy Center Fund for New American Plays 1990 -1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Latino Theatre Initiative 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lujan, Jaime 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Madrid, Dolores [Ancestral Moon Productions] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Miracle Theatre Group, Portland 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mixed Blood Theatre Company, Minneapolis [Kunz, David] 1991 Fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mueller, Amy n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1990 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - New Dramatists, New York n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pacific Theatre Ensemble 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ramirez, Lisa 1993 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Recording and Research Center [Bastillor, Barbara] 1994 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Repertorio Español [Gorostiza, Felipe] 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Salinas River New Works Festival 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - San Jose Repertory Theatre 1993 Aug. 10 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - South Coast Repertory, Costa Mesa, California [Shadow of a Man] 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - South Coast Repertory, Costa Mesa, California 1991 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Teatro Vista c. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Theatre Communications Group, Inc. [includes: Play Source.--Vol. 10, nos. 3 - 4; vol. 11, no. 5] 1989 -1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Theatre Forum [Huerta, Jorge] 1992 Jan. 24 -Feb. 4 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Theatre Rhinoceros, San Francisco [Giving up the ghost] 1988 -1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Women's Project and Productions, New York 1989 Oct. 31 -1991 Dec. 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Series IX. Academic Work
  - Journals: education journal 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journals: Calligraphy class, Immaculate Heart College n.d. [c. 1971] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "A comparison of Thomas More's 'Utopia' with George Orwell's '1984'" 1970 Dec. 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Papers: on "The Ruined Cottage" by William Wordsworth c. 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    AMs, 6 pp.
  - Undergraduate Papers: papers for "American Short Story" 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Ms, 12 pp.
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Analysis of William Blake's 'London'" 1971 Feb. 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "An analysis of Matthew Arnold's 'Dover Beach'" 1971 Mar. 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Charles Dickens' 'Hard Times' - A comic satire" 1971 Apr. 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Adulthood -- The Dark Woods *** The Stoney End" 1971 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Papers: on Romeo and Juliet 1971 Oct. 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Beatrice of Much Ado about Nothing" 1971 Nov. 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "The most serious mistake my parents made with me" 1972 Mar. 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Papers: on "Death of a Salesman" and other compositions 1972 Feb. -Mar. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    AMs, 8 pp.
  - Undergraduate Papers: "A comparison of characterizations: Quentin Compson of William Faulkner's 'The Sound and the Fury' and Jake Barnes of Ernest Hemmingway's [sic] 'The Sun Also Rises'" 1972 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Basic skills for WW" -- creative writing assignments 1972 Sept. -Nov. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    13 AMs, 23 pp.
  - Undergraduate Papers: "The contemporary Quixote view of Women's Liberation" 1973 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    AMs, 5 pp.
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Story within a story" 1973 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "An analysis of 'I, Maximus of Gloucester, to you' by Charles Olson, 1950" 1973 Oct. 18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "An analysis of 'The name' by Robert Creeley" 1973 Nov. 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "Kenneth Koch: a colorful comic poet, with serious intentions" 1974 Jan. 10 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "An analysis of 'To stay alive,' a collection of poems by Denise Levertov" 1974 Jan. 23 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Papers: "From the Tramp to Calvero" 1974 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Creative writing - Drama: "Barbara and Ralph" [with Jeanne di Giorgio] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Creative writing - Drama: "Our play" [with Jeanne di Giorgio] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Class notes: Film history 111b 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ephemera: Immaculate Heart College Commencement Program 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Class notes: History 625 - History of Feminism, Dr. Mary Lowenthal Felstiner [1 of 2] 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Class notes: History 625 - History of Feminism, Dr. Mary Lowenthal Felstiner [2 of 2] 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Class notes: English 614 - Woman as Hero 1978 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Class notes: Speech Communication 503 - Sex roles and communication & SC746.01 Patriarchal Rhetoric; Sally Gearhart [1 of 2] 1978 Fall -1979 Spring (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Class notes: Speech Communication 503 - Sex roles and communication & SC746.01 Patriarchal Rhetoric; Sally Gearhart [2 of 2] 1978 Fall -1979 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Creative prose] "Leah's story, the first book" 1978 Oct. 5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Creative prose] "Sex roles in communication" 1978 Oct. 16 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Creative prose] "The Alchemy, a creation myth" 1978 Oct. 17 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [essays] "A definition of Lesbian" [1978 Oct. 17] (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Woman as Hero] "The mill on the floss: George Eliot's Unborn Dark Truth" 1978 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Creative Prose] "From the Journal entry of the Feminist Revolutionary, María Moraga 26 Nov., 1.A.F.R." [1978 Nov. 26?] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Woman as Hero] "Lesbianism as heroic impulse: a comparative analysis of two woman heroes: Lily Briscoe, of Virginia Woolf's 'To the Lighthouse' and Su, of June Arnold's 'Sister Gin'" 1978 Nov. 28 -Dec. 16 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Creative Prose] "Cherríe Moraga, revolutionary and writer dies in auto crash at the age of 67" 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "'Still resisting': 5 (well) selected poems" 1978 Dec. 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "In search of a better word: the war between monogamy and non-monogamy" 1979 Jan. 31 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "'This we were, this is how we tried to love': a review of 'The Ladies if Llangollen' by Elizabeth Mavor" 1979 Jan. 31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "Toward a community of survivors; or, the revolution begins at home" 1979 Easter (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "Gertrude Stein: a revolutionary Sappho or 'The Mother of us all'" 1979 Spring (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "'I am Adrienne': In the name of all Women: an exploration of the writings of Adrienne Rich" 1979 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
    TMs, 21 pp.
  - San Francisco State University papers: [Essays] "A synthesis of Sappho" [1978 -1979] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Class notes: Women's Studies 550: Lesbian History and Biography, H. V. Wenzel [1 of 3] 1979 Spring (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Class notes: Women's Studies 550: Lesbian History and Biography, H. V. Wenzel [2 of 3] 1979 Spring (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Class notes: Women's Studies 550: Lesbian History and Biography, H. V. Wenzel [3 of 3] 1979 Spring (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Class notes: Feminist Thought 1979 Fall (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class notes: Women's Studies 100: Women and Society, Barbara Smith 1981 Spring (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 180, University of California, Berkeley: Advanced Expository Writing 1980 Fall (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Teaching materials: syllabus for Lesbian Literature and Feminism 1980 Fall (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Teaching materials: Lesbian Literature and Feminism, Student writings [i.e., bibliographies] 1980 Fall (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Teaching materials: Lesbian Literature and Feminism, research notes and materials 1980 Fall (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Teaching materials: Women's Studies 550, Lesbian of Color Literature 1986 Fall (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Teaching materials: Hispanic Women Writers (Latina Literature) 1987 Winter (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Teaching materials: miscellaneous student papers 1986 May 6 -1989 Oct. 31; n.d. (Box 2, Folder 23)